#哈喽大家好我是王刚
Hello everyone, I'm Wang Gang
#最近有粉丝私信我说你为什么没有更新
Recently some fans have been messaging me about why I stopped updating
#大家可以看到我现在戴着口罩说话
As you can see, I am talking with a mask
#确实不是很方便
It is indeed not very convenient (to make videos)
#因为这个疫情的关系呢
Because of the coronavirus outbreak
#我从（1月）17号就一直在家里面
I've been staying at home since 17th January
#几乎没有出门
I seldom went out
#也没有回老家
I didn't go back to my hometown either
#未来的话
In the future...
#等这次疫情过去了会继续拍摄一些
I'll shoot some new videos after this epidemic is over
#做菜的一些短视频
Some short videos about cooking
#跟以前的风格也保持一样
I'll stick to my style in the past
#然后会增加一些厨房小百科的一些厨房小知识吧
And I'm going to make more content about culinary tips and tricks
#很多粉丝在问我们开店的事情
Many fans are also asking me when I'm gonna open a restaurant
#其实大家也看得到因为这次疫情嘛
Actually, you can also see that, (progress is halted) due to the epidemic
#我们去年找了一个门店
We found a spot for lease last year
#都已经到了签合同这一步
And we were at the step of signing the contract
#然后发现这个苗头不对就没有（继续）做
But something didn't feel right so we stopped
#如果是做了的话我估计现在也是开不了张
Even if I signed the contract, I don't think I would have been able to open it
#餐饮这一块今年肯定会进行一个洗牌
There will definitely be a shuffle in the restaurant industry
#现在（我）也不打算做太大型的家常菜的一个餐厅
For now I don't want to run a large restaurant that provides home dishes
#还有一个（停更）原因就是说
Another reason (for stopping updating) is that
#我老婆生（孩子）了
My wife just gave birth
#生了个小弟弟
to a little boy
#现在名字还没取好
Now we haven't given him a name yet
#你们也可以帮我想想
You can also help me come up with one
#（现在）街上很多门面都关了
Now many shops are closed
#除了菜市场还有一些生活必要的一些门店开着
Except for farmers markets and some grocery stores
#应该是从（正月）初一吧
This started on the first day of Chinese new year
#（我）都没有去任何地方走动
I haven't been anywhere since then
#这段时间的话因为疫情比较严重
These days, since the epidemic is more severe
#我们这个县城还好
Actually it's ok in this small town
#只出现确诊了一个（新冠肺炎感染者）
There is only one confirmed case of coronavirus
#我们县县领导的（管控）工作做得非常棒
The leader of the local government did a very good job
#这个是防范于未然嘛
The key is to nip it from the bud
#所以呢我们在家
So even if we are staying at home
#就算不出门
Not going out
#也要保持窗户通风 勤洗手
We should keep the room well-ventilated and wash our hands frequently
#炒菜的话一定要多炒一会儿把它炒熟
When cooking, make sure it's fully cooked
#这样可以避免一些不必要的麻烦
such that we can avoid some unnecessary trouble
#好啦 现在我带你们看一下我们这个县城现在是什么样子
Ok. Now let me show you what this town looks like
#要是平时的话
Normally during this time
#不说人山人海
Even if it's not extremely crowded
#那肯定是人流量非常大的
There must be a lot of people
#我们现在看得到这县城里面人烟稀少
Now we can see that there are just a few people around
#大家都呆在家里
as everyone is staying at home